<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Rishabh Kumar</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Rishabh Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Copyright Rishabh Kumar &lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Github Co-pilot - pros and cons</title>
      <link>/post/creating-ml-apps-with-github-co-pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/creating-ml-apps-with-github-co-pilot/</guid>
      <description>Recently I got hold of a beta version of GitHub co-pilot. GitHub Copilot is an AI pair programmer that helps you write code faster and with less work. GitHub Copilot draws context from comments and code, and suggests individual lines and whole functions instantly. GitHub Copilot is powered by OpenAI Codex, a new AI system created by OpenAI.
It really feels quite magical to use. please see the gif below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Health among British adults since March</title>
      <link>/post/mental-health-among-british-adults-since-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mental-health-among-british-adults-since-march/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are Random Forest?</title>
      <link>/post/what-are-random-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/what-are-random-forest/</guid>
      <description>noDraft
Random forest algorithm helps us to classify items into various groupings.There are two kinds of random forest algorithms: one for regression and one for classifications. Both have similar underlying philosophies.
Before getting into random forest its important to know the workings of the Decision tree algorithm. It works in a way to find features that will split the data in resulting groups that are as different from each other and the members of th these groups are as similar to each other as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representation of women in comics</title>
      <link>/post/representation-of-women-in-comics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/representation-of-women-in-comics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treatment disparities of Blacks</title>
      <link>/post/treatment-disparities-of-blacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/treatment-disparities-of-blacks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Countries back on the move</title>
      <link>/post/countries-back-on-the-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/countries-back-on-the-move/</guid>
      <description>It has been 112 days since WHO declared the new Coronavirus epidemic as a pandemic. Since then we saw multiple countries imposing partial lockdowns to make people work from home more to completete shutdowns of their nations where people were only allowed to leave their homes for bare essestials.
Since then a lot has happened. There is a small hope that vaccines will be out soon and some european countries have started opening up their economies too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democracies in the time of Covid</title>
      <link>/post/democracies-in-the-time-of-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/democracies-in-the-time-of-covid/</guid>
      <description>Over the past weeks I have had conversation with families and friends about coronavirus and about how different governments are responding to the challenge. One point that was mentioned often in the discussion was that its the countries with stronger government that have stayed off the crisis whereas democratic countries are the ones who cannot fight off the pandemic. Just because democracies make it slow.
I live in a democracy and believe in democracies 💕 so I did find this idea a bit off-putting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geslatt Principles</title>
      <link>/post/geslatt-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/geslatt-principles/</guid>
      <description>Gestalt (means form, shape in German) is a group of visual perception principles developed by German psychologists in 1920s. It is built on the theory that “an organized whole, is perceived as greater than the sum of its parts”.
Principles Emergence People tend to identify elements first in their general outlined form. Our brain recognises a simple, well-defined object quicker than a detailed one.
Multi-Stability People will often interpret ambiguous objects in more than one ways.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
